Quang Tran

Full Stack Engineer

Website

https://chop.dev

Email m@chop.dev

Telegram

https://t.me/choptran

Ho Chi Minh (+84) 0912221396

Self-motivated Software Developer bringing forth over 7 years of experience. In love with the art of creating great software, easy to understand, stable and resilient. Experienced in working between backend and frontend teams to ensure all the goals of a project are achieved and met within scope.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address: District 1, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Date of birth: Ho Chi Minh

Driving License: Full

Hobbies: Running, Weight Lifting, Starcraft, Dota, Chess, Poker.

LANGUAGES

★★★★★ Vietnamese ★★★★★ English

SKILLS

★★★★ Vue / Angular / React ★★★★ Javascript / Typescript ★★★★ Firebase ★★★★ Flutter ★★★★ GCP / AWS Stack ★★★☆ Go lang

```
★★☆☆ Python
★★☆☆ Rust
★★☆☆ Haskell
★★☆☆ Kubernetes
★★★☆☆ Cardano Blockchain
★★★☆☆ Ethereum Blockchain
```

WORK EXPERIENCE

* August 2020 - Present

FE Developer at LINE Corp,

Healthcare ecosystem: Build Doctor booking and review, Hospital Search, Symptom Checks, Online Diagnostics with VueJs.

- Manage and Coordinate a sub-team for Line Healthcare Front end apps
- Work with Japanese and Korean planner to archive sprint goals
- Work with QA team to make sure the quality of final product

Team size: 20

* March 2021 - Present

Binance Trading System at LINA TRAN Stake Pool, Ho Chi Minh City

Design and build trading System to automate the trading process of a trader group.

Using Mathematics formulas to Dollar Cost Average sell and buy orders. Currently apply with BinanceAPI.

Teamsize: 5

* February 2019 - July 2020

Full Stack Developer at ChatQ SG, Ho Chi Minh

- Build a management system for financial bots on the Kubernetes cluster.
- Migrate KONG API Gateway to GCP Cloud Endpoints.
- Build user online API in Go Lang and Python.
- Created an internal Dashboard for monitoring the infrastructure of the Back-end using React and Material UI.
- Build and manage monitoring systems with Datadog.
- Refactor the existing website chatq.sg using VueJs framework

Team size: 15

* October 2018 - January 2019

Front end Software Engineer at LOCTOC PTE LTD, Singapore

Develop an Angular Dashboard for KnowNuggets app (www.getknowapp.com).

Improve the logic between components and rework the layout.

Team size: 3

* August 2017 - September 2018

Developer at H&M Media, Ho Chi Minh

Develop CMS for news website nhavaxe.vn using customized QuillJs and Angular5. Develop a survey web app for Coffee Bean & Tea Leaf's Tet holiday survey using ReactJS.

* May 2015 - April 2017

Marketing Officer at Tokyo Deli - Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh Manage restaurant service and coordinate with Japanese experts.

- Customer service lead
- Design menu and website using Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.

* June 2014 - June 2015

Web programer at VinaCIS Group (vinacis.com)

EDUCATION

- * September 2009 June 2013 University of Birmingham, Birmingham BSc Computer Science
- * September 2007 June 2009 University of Birmingham, Birmingham Foundation course at School of Electronic and Electrical Engineering

REFERENCES

- * Jerome Siv from ChatQ SG jerome.siv@chatq.sg
- * Krish Sridhar from Loctoc Pte Ltd krish@knownuggets.com
- * Eytan Schmal from WeDidIt Solutions eytan.schmal@wediditsolutions.com
- +84 0937479182
- * Pham Truong Tho from H&M Media truongtho@hmmedia.com.vn
- +84 0975370297
- * Ryo Ozawa from Tokyo Deli Vietnam ryo.ozawa@tokyodeli.com.vn
- +81 07015971216